<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Posts on sre.kz</title>
		<link>https://sre.kz/posts/</link>
		<description>Recent content in Posts on sre.kz</description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<atom:link href="https://sre.kz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>Simple personal CI/CD</title>
			<link>https://sre.kz/posts/simple-personal-cicd/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://sre.kz/posts/simple-personal-cicd/</guid>
			<description>Here i want to share how my personal cicd works. Thanks to Golang it costs me only 5$ digitalocean instance which runs - traefik, grafana, promethues, loki and my personal sites. Hope it will be helpful&amp;hellip;
First of all list of used tools:
 Traefik - as reverse proxy with lets encrypt Github - as git repository Docker Hub - as docker images registry, and build tool Watchtower - refreshes running container with new version  You can find all of the code here</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here i want to share how my personal cicd works. Thanks to Golang it costs me only 5$ digitalocean instance which runs - traefik, grafana, promethues, loki and my personal sites. Hope it will be helpful&hellip;</p>
<p>First of all list of used tools:</p>
<ul>
<li>Traefik - as reverse proxy with lets encrypt</li>
<li>Github - as git repository</li>
<li>Docker Hub - as docker images registry, and build tool</li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/containrrr/watchtower">Watchtower</a> - refreshes running container with new version</li>
</ul>
<p>You can find all of the code <a href="https://github.com/anuar45/srekz">here</a></p>
<p>For now briefly, will add more later:</p>
<ul>
<li>Code pushed to github with version tag</li>
<li>Code tested with Github actions</li>
<li>Docker Hub monitors and build tagged versions</li>
<li>Watchtower monitors and pulls new docker image, restarts existing one with updated version</li>
<li>Traefik monitors running contrainers and expose them with lets encrypt certs</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>My First Post</title>
			<link>https://sre.kz/posts/my-first-post/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://sre.kz/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
			<description>Right now idea is to make posts about exploring code and architecture of popular Golang projects.
Plus some random toughts, which could be helpful to anyone.
Also will mirror this to popular blog platforms.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Right now idea is to make posts about exploring code and architecture of popular Golang projects.</p>
<p>Plus some random toughts, which could be helpful to anyone.</p>
<p>Also will mirror this to popular blog platforms.</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
